<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RealisedGains Feed</title>
    <link>https://t.me/realisedgains</link>
    <description>RSS feed for @realisedgains</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Like I said, $BABA earnings beat. Big time. We kee...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2400</link>
      <description>Like I said, $BABA earnings beat. Big time. We keep holding China 🫡🐉</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2400</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**Why I am still long China 🇨🇳**
Gave it to you gu...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2401</link>
      <description>**Why I am still long China 🇨🇳**
Gave it to you guys 4 Months ago with my Average $BABA buys at $69-74 publicly on Youtube and on X predicting 130-140 in Q1 2025. We are here **now**. Not claiming to be good, just sharing 🤙🏼 Specifically I've said before I am only selling covered calls on these, not selling.

Source: [TLDR Long China](https://youtu.be/MDvJ8kKy9Dk?si=swq7ek_wW9PBzG1x)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2401</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[We have come full circle.](https://www.linkedin.c...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2402</link>
      <description>[We have come full circle.](https://www.linkedin.com/posts/seowie_8-years-later-catching-up-with-the-eric-activity-7298362076148772865--AB5?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;rcm=ACoAACZx0akBV9rvy2EuYjg6g1ALPz1hwOhtNq4) 
Do feel free to engage &amp; connect with me on Linkedin as well 😊</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2402</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**$NIO**** Prediction**
Earnings date: 03/05/2025
...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2403</link>
      <description>**$NIO**** Prediction**
Earnings date: 03/05/2025

Bull Case (Leaning towards this):
Given deliveries (known at 72,689) and stimulus tailwinds, NIO likely beats revenue at $2.9-$3 billion. Margins improve to 11%-12% due to alloy savings, yielding -$0.30 EPS. The stock’s lack of pre-earnings run-up suggests a 20%-30% pop to $5.10-$5.50 if guidance excites (e.g., 440,000 units for 2025, Firefly/ET9 traction). Post-earnings, $5.50-$6 by April 2025 is feasible if macro holds.

Bear Case:
If price wars hit harder than expected, Q4 revenue undershoots at $2.7 billion (below $2.8B consensus), with margins slipping to 9% due to ONVO’s low ASPs and discounting, resulting in -$0.45 EPS. Guidance disappoints at 380,000 units for 2025 with profitability pushed beyond Q4 2025. The stock drops 10%-15% to $3.80-$3.60, with tariff fears and a Hang Seng pullback capping recovery; a slide to $3 or below is possible by April 2025 if sentiment sours further.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2403</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**Where I see markets headed**:
**Dollar Devaluati...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2404</link>
      <description>**Where I see markets headed**:
**Dollar Devaluation: **I expect the dollar to weaken without Fed rate hikes or cuts, preserving the current 4.25-4.5% range. This stasis aids devaluing the $36T debt, reducing its real burden.
**Musk &amp; DOGE: **Elon Musk’s DOGE will likely enforce austerity, slashing $2T from spending. This curbs deficits, creating space for future rate cuts if needed.
**Monetary Policy: **I foresee a continued pause on rate cuts in 2025, but backdoor QE will emerge—draining the Reverse Repo ($350B) and Treasury General Account ($700B). These moves inject liquidity, support markets, and subtly weaken the dollar.

**Market Outlook:** I think Bonds have bottomed, unless Japan and China continues to unwind positions to bolster purchasing of gold. Silver will start creeping up, running up on the lag on gold as well. Crypto still has another leg up. US Equities as well but not before a pullback. However, imo 2nd half of the year feels dicey, primed for a larger correction.

Source: [Talking Gold &amp; Precious Metals](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VGFu7ENJ3G0&amp;)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2404</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**ByBit just hacked for potentially 1.3 Billion in...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2405</link>
      <description>**ByBit just hacked for potentially 1.3 Billion in Ethereum**
Bybit confirmed a sophisticated attack on Feb 21, 2025, targeting an ETH multisig cold wallet during a transfer to a warm wallet. The signing interface was spoofed, hiding altered smart contract logic that redirected funds to an unknown address.  

A digital asset security platform might have prevented this. Solutions like Fireblocks use Multi-Party Computation (MPC), replacing multisig’s on-chain vulnerabilities with off-chain signing and air-gapped cold storage, BitGo’s multisig with cold storage, Anchorage’s HSM-backed custody, and Copper’s MPC-hybrid also bolster security could have fixed this. 

Just some shoddy security overall… Bybit’s setup likely lacked these, exposing a single point of failure.  

**Exact losses (rumoured $1.4B)** are unclear, but the breach underscores a need for layered defenses beyond basic multisig. **This is looking bearish on Crypto**, given the falling US equities and Bond Markets pricing in some end February weakness on risk assets as well.

Source: [ByBit confirms Eth Hack](https://www.realisedgains.com/blog/bybit-just-got-hacked-for-potentially-1-3-billion-in-ethereum)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2405</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is HUGE 🩸 — larger than any prior single cryp...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2407</link>
      <description>This is HUGE 🩸 — larger than any prior single crypto hack (e.g., Ronin’s $620 million, Coincheck’s $534 million).

1/8 of FTX's collapse HUGE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2407</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**Bybit $1.5B hacker exposed**
Sleuths proved it w...</title>
      <link>https://t.me/realisedgains/2411</link>
      <description>**Bybit $1.5B hacker exposed**
Sleuths proved it was North Korea’s Lazarus Group, linked to Park Jin Hyok, stole 401K+ ETH ($1.46 Billion worth) via a fake UI exploit. Evidence shows test txs, wallet forensics, &amp; timing tied to Lazarus’ past hacks.

Laundering $1.46B? Tough. Tornado Cash? Sanctioned &amp; watched. Extremely difficult to move this size without risking exposure. 

Bybit now sees $2.235B in total outflows today—hacked funds + user withdrawals panicking post-breach! 

**My 2 cents is that this is not a FTX situation - I believe ByBit is solvent, but this is a tough hole to recover from!**

In other news: COVID 2.0 strain detected in China— likely some continuation of this dip given so much FUD coinciding at once.

Source: [Stocks Dip on New Covid Fears](https://www.realisedgains.com/blog/stocks-dip-as-new-virus-fears-emerge)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2411</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
